EFEAKPOR OGHENETEGA

Address: No 5 Pastor Paul Street, Off Okpanam Road, Asaba, Delta State. Nigeria

E-mail: teefwesh0@gmail.com Phone: **+2348168594341**

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

A brilliant Frontend Web developer with 2 years of progressive experience in Website Design and Development.

A highly motivated and enthusiastic individual with proven experience; highly articulated and effective communicator; work well with individuals on all levels; a resourceful person, problem solver and team player, seeking opportunities to create social change, proffer innovative solutions and build corporate relationships that accelerate corporate growth.

SKILLS:

- MySQL | MongoDb | JavaScript | React.js | MERN | HTML | CSS
- Paying good attention to details
- Excellent communication and organizational skills
- Ability to work without supervision

WORKING EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER Sept 2020 - Till Date

Key Responsibility

- Development of Website Project
- Developing Responsive web pages
- Presenting Project work to client

FEDERAL MORTGAGE BANK | IT Student

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020

Key Responsibility

• Data Entry

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS OBTAINED WITH DATES:

Ordinary National Diploma (OND) Computer Science

2019 - 2021

Delta State Polytechnic, Ogwashi Uku

REFEREES:

Available on Request